1. There is a river and some trees near my home.
There is a river and some trees near my home.
2. We can make snowmen in winter.
We can make snowmen in winter.
3. They are heroes who put themselves in harm's way.
They are heroes who put themselves in harm's way.
4. Students give some cards to their teachers on Teacher's Day.
Students give some cards to their teachers on Teacher's Day.
5. It is our duty to protect
或“
the wild animals.
give Teacher's 6.
第二部分：听五个句子，分别选择其相应的应答语，并在答题卡的相应位
置将其字母序号涂。
每个句子读两遍。
每个句子读完后，分别有十秒钟的答题时间。
Thank you for your help.
7. Good luck to you.
8. What are you going to do during this summer?
What are you going to do during this summer?
9. What's the date today?
What's the date today?
10. What is your father like?
What is your father like?
第三部分：听下列五段对话，根据对话内容及备选的问题，选择正确选项
，并在答题卡的相应位置将其字母序号涂黑。
每段对话读两遍。
每。
但对话读完后，分别有十秒钟的答题时间。
11. When will we arrive in Let me see.
It's half past eight.
Our plane will land in 20 minutes.
When will the two persons get to Tongren?
12. When will the two persons get to Tongren?
12. Could you please email your menu to me?
My address is mariaat126.com.
Could you please email your menu to me?
13. What's the woman's email address?
13. Could you have a table for four?
Sorry, there's only a table for three left.
Would you please wait for a minute?
Could you please email your menu address mariaat126.com.
14. Hi Michael, what's your dream job?
Oh Jane, it's hard to say.
It's good to be a doctor but I prefer to be a
Hi Michael, what's your dream job?
Oh Jane, it's hard to say.
It's good to be a but I prefer to be a
15. Michael's dream job?
15. What are you doing, Kung Kung?
I'm playing Glory King game.
It's very interesting.
No, I don't agree.
I think it's boring.
Question. What does the woman think of Glory King game?
What are you doing, Kung I'm playing Glory King game.
It's very interesting.
No, I don't agree.
I think it's boring.
Question. What does the woman think of Glory King game?
第四部分，听下面一篇短文，根据短文内容和所提问题选择。
得正确答案，并在答题卡的相应位置将其字母序号涂黑。
短文读两遍。
短文读完后，有六十秒钟的答题时间。
When I have something difficult to do, I used to ask my mom,
Could you help me?
But she always says,
Do it yourself, dear.
Then I got so sad.
I used to think she was a lazy mother.
For example, one day I invited some friends to my home.
My bedroom was untidy.
Books were all over the table and the ground.
So I asked my mother to help me clean it.
But she said seriously,
Do it yourself, girl.
So I did it myself.
Because of my lazy mother, I wash my clothes and clean my room myself.
I can also help my parents do some housework.
From now on, I understand my mother.
It's her laziness that makes me clever and hardworking.
Just as my mother says, A lady can't be lazy or she'll be crazy.
Work can make you sunny.
I have a great mother.
A good mother is a good teacher.
When I have something difficult to do, I used to ask my mom,
Could you help me?
But she always says, Do it yourself, dear.
Then I got so sad.
I used to think she was a lazy mother.
For example, one day I invited some friends to my home.
My bedroom was untidy.
Books were all over the table and the ground.
So I asked my mother to help me clean it.
But she said seriously,
Do it yourself, girl.
So I did it myself.
Because of my lazy mother, I wash my clothes and clean my room myself.
I can also help my parents do some housework.
From now on, I understand my mother.
It's her laziness that makes me clever and hardworking.
Just as my mother says,
A lady can't be lazy or she'll be crazy.
Work can make you sunny.
I have a great mother.
A good mother is a good teacher.
Thank you for watching.
听力二。
watching. Learning is a lifelong journey.
各位考生请注意，本部分试题在卷二七十一至七十五小题。
各。
为考生请注意，本部分试题在卷二七十一至七十五小题。
听下面一篇短文，根据。
所听到的短文内容，填写表格，
每空一词。
答案务必书写在答题卡卷二各小题规定的位置。
短文读两遍。
We all want to know how to learn better.
I hope my advice can help you a little.
First, have some learning plans before exams.
This could be from one month to six months.
The time length depends on the importance of the exam.
If you're learning for the final exam,
you'd better make a one -month plan.
Second, think about your environment.
Make sure the place where you're going to learn is comfortable with enough light.
However, if you're that kind of person that likes listening to music while learning,
you have to find out what kind of music works best for you.
Generally speaking, you'd better choose classical music instead of pop or rock
music. Third, have enough rest.
If you learn for too long, your mind will work less effectively.
Many people suggested learning an hour with a 10 -minute break.
Learning is a lifelong journey.
We all want to know how to learn better.
I hope my advice can help you a
First, have some learning plans before exams.
This could be from one month to six months.
The time length depends on the importance of the exam.
If you're learning for the final exam, you'd better make a one -month plan.
Second, think about your environment.
Make sure the place where you're going to learn is comfortable with enough light.
However, if you're that kind of person that likes listening to music while learning,
you have to find out what kind of music works best for you.
Generally speaking, you'd better choose classical music instead of pop or rock
music. Third, have enough rest.
If you learn for too long, your mind will work less effectively.
Many people suggested learning an hour with a 10 -minute break.